{
    "id": "575a443b5c924a479b86a02c6f557dcc",
    "title": "Conjunctions And Relative Pronouns Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Her clothes caught fire ................................................. she was cooking in the kitchen.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "while",
                "since",
                "whereas"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0571418eb40f44eaa2c3dc161b162d9c"
        },
        {
            "question": "........................................... his sons are employed, he has no financial worries.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "That",
                "Now that",
                "So that"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "812897e2616d4e47bb109d4e93c91835"
        },
        {
            "question": "He does not know any language ........................................... Hindi.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "apart",
                "except",
                "expect"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "00dd517a5ddb4c8bb84b28eb51607a2d"
        },
        {
            "question": "........................................... I invited them, they did not come.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Even if",
                "Even though",
                "If"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f35e80b7f27d4fd189026fcd2905a534"
        },
        {
            "question": "............................................... the weather was bad, he went out.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "As though",
                "Though"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "be0bfb1641084194aa1e0fc03b0c61a7"
        },
        {
            "question": "Julius Caesar, .................................................. came to Britain in 55 BC, was a powerful Roman General.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "that",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2d8b8116f6c5462ba0c7bc7069850645"
        },
        {
            "question": "........................................... the clock struck twelve, I went to bed.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "When",
                "Since",
                "Until"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "19034fa0e0334e5f8700dcbc3654943d"
        },
        {
            "question": "Napoleon, ............................................. the French honor very much, died at St. Helena.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "whom",
                "which",
                "that"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9d8b6f2f1bfb415bb72e91dc8e3726cc"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the new computer ............................................... my father bought yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "what",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3aa732df68dc4321961e746da9f10285"
        },
        {
            "question": "The village ......................................... we live is infested with rats.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "where",
                "that",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7874f390cb5e451b80b268a4e5817ed0"
        }
    ]
}